

WINSMER ONEAL MARTE ADAMES

| CONTACT |
|--|
| C/central #38, Anateresa Balaguer, SDE, RD. |
| P: 829-250-3080 |
| e: oneal.marte1801@gmail.com |
| w: https://oneal1801.github.io/public/index.html |
| |
| SOCIAL - |
| f facebook.com/oneal.marte/ |
| github.com/oneal1801 |
| in linkedin.com/in/wmartea/ |
| instagram.com/oneal180118/ |
| CKILLC |
| SKILLS ——— |
| Adobe PS AI PR |
| SASS CSS HTML5 |
| Js Ts NodeJs |
| Angular Vue React |
| C# WebApi RestApi |
| Java EJB JSF Sprint |
| SQL PL SQL Oracle |
| Git Scrum Agile |
| Xamarin ReactNativ |
| Communication |
| Problem Solving |
| Teamwork |
| Creativity |
| |
| HOBBIES — |
| |
| |

Watching Movie | Listening Music

Photography | Video Recording & Editing

ABOUT

I'm Winsmer Oneal My specialties include quickly learning new skills and programming languages, problem solving, responsive design principles, website optimization and the Model View View Model (MVVM) and Model View Controller (MVC) methods of organizing code.

My personal goal is mastering the different development techniques and necessary tools that could help me satisfy the goals set by me and the company that I'm working for.

3+ years experience with Java, EBJ, JFS, Oracle, PL/SQL, PrimeFaces. 4+ Years experience with C#, MS SQL, ASP MVC, REST Api, Web Services, JavaScript, Bootstrap 5.

1++ Year working with Angular 8+, TypeScript, Net Core 5.

EDUCATION

ENGINEER'S DEGREE, SYSTEM ENGINEERING

Dominican University O&M | Dominican Republic | 2010 - 2015

ENGLISH INMERSION PROGRAM

University APEC | Dominican Republic | 2010 - 2011

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR SOFTWARE ANALYST

EDESUR Dominicana S.A | Dominican Republic | 2017 - Current Providing analysis, design, documentation, testing and best practices for the company needs.

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER

TicVelopers | USA | 2018 - Current

Worknig as freelance on TicVelopers to customers from initial design to deployment.

SENIOR SUPPORT TECHNICIAN

Avaya | Dominican Republic | 2013 - 2017

Working as tier 2 engineer, collecting logs, giving the first contact to the direct customers to then escalate the case to the tier 3 backbone engineer. Applied KB solutions to customers before raising the case to the next level support.